sportarena.gr 2004-12-04

# Privacy notice

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

Sport Arena knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting www.sportarena.gr, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Sport Arena    
Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Sport Arena. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.

  * **Automatic Information**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses www.sportarena.gr. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a   
personalized experience at www.e-sportarena.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

  * **Information from Other Sources**  
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), or getting better known with our customers so to serve them more efficiently, from sources such as member applications.

**What About Cookies?**  

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.  

  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Sport Arena's coolest features,   
and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**Does Sport Arena Share the Information It Receives?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others.

  * **Agents**  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform   
functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders,   
delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.  

  * **Business Transfers**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Sport Arena, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.  

  * **Protection of Sport Arena and Others**  
We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Sport Arena, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.   

  * **With Your Consent**  
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when   
information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.  

  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.   

  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

  * **What Choices Do I Have?**

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase at Sport Arena site.

  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**Children**  
Sport Arena does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Sport Arena only with involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit www.sportarena.gr, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Hellenic Republic and the European Union. If you have any concern about privacy at Sport Arena, please send us a thorough description through our contact page and feedback@e-sportarena.com and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
